and thoughts time hello great this day
и думы время привет здорово this day
greeting how normal it is you don’t
приветственно как сам нормально это не
get sick at a time what things are you doing
хвораешь что за раз дела какие у тебя мы
where are we from here I’m from ukraine the city of
откуда вот я из украины города
khmelnitsky madrasah and from somewhere without a father
хмельницкий медресе и откуда-то без отец
well you are not a father you are almost the
ну ты ты ты не отец ты мне один почти
same age as me on the press board  he is this I am burning
ровесник на доске дави он это это я горю
from odessa hello
с одессы привет
sensibly squeezed together
здраво дружно сжал
sorry sorry nicknamed from russia I am social security
извини-извини прозван из россии я собес
yes
да
what to do there you will open the days of
какие там делать вы откроешь дней
ukraine the city of khmelnitsky you are from
украины города хмельницкий вы из
russian i russia the city of lipetsk
российской я россия город липецк
and where are you now giving up are
а где вы сейчас отдастся находитесь
we now or the lipetsk region
мы сейчас или липецкая область
what is needed here  we find the family where
надо чему тут находим семьей где ты
you are on the coals worry about the rations
находишься на угли беспокойся рационов
once calm down what are
один раз успакойся чё
you there like an idiot look at me and you
вас там как идиот посмотрите на я а вы
can try the Russian elements of
можете попробовать русские элементы
inserting French speech I don’t
вставки французской речи я не совсем
quite understand well, sorry, I’m a little
сильно понимаю ну ты извини я немножко
burr I meant brother Savannah
картавлю я имел ввиду братом саванна
asthmatics I’m all I understand  I express myself
астматики я все я понятно выражаюсь все
purely simply as a kind of refueling lady so
чисто просто рода заправки дамы чтобы
that, as two polite people at the
дабы как два вежливых человека на
inspection
осмотре
of people from Russia, I’ll ask how you feel
у людей из россии спрошу как вы
about the war uk  In the rain,
относитесь к войне украине
it’s a question of
это вопрос
how I feel about the war in Ukraine before
как я отношусь к войне на украине до бук
Lenin’s beech,
ленина
look, I can not only think I
смотри я могу не то что могу я двояко
’m ambivalent, that is, 1 on the one hand, here’s the
отношусь то есть 1 с одной стороны вот
map to say such saying
карте сказать такие говорить
Ukraine has always been our brotherly
украина всегда была нашим братским
people, we have
народом вот
always, always respected honored and
всегда-всегда мы уважали чтили и
not only  respected honored with a coin there,
не только уважали чтили монеткой там не
well, and between investments we all supported in Ukraine
ну и между инвестиции все мы в украину
in the Soviet Union, we passed how we take
в советском союзе мы сдали как берем
facial expressions to me something very much,
выражение лица мне что-то очень уж
he doesn’t interrupt you, let’s say,
он не перебивать вас давайте да говорите
but in a
но во
second opinion what
второе мнение какое
agreement could be agreed in any case,
договориться в любом случае можно было
well, not  starting a war without starting what to
ну вот не начиная войны не начиная чего
agree, it was possible,
договориться же можно было
well, you yourself, how do you think you will finish, I don’t
ну ты сам как думаешь вы закончите я не
interrupt emotions, you write down
перебивать эмоций ты записываешь
here, agree in any case, it
вот договориться в любом случае можно
was possible, in any case, it was possible, that
было в любом случае можно был вот то
is, there was enough time for all
есть времени достаточно было на все эти
these things, here is an
вот дела вот
attack, that is, non-aggression  I’ll even
нападение то есть ненападении даже
formulate in a different way
сформулирую по-другому
specifically Russia’s operations on the territory of
специально операции россии на территории
Ukraine,
украины
here’s
вот
my opinion, it was
мое мнение она была необходима
necessary for
необходимо
NATO countries, it’s just already in  now you know how to
страны нато просто уже встали знаешь как
say it's enough just to
сказать достаточно только ворота
knock on the door here you
постучать в дверь нах вот вы здесь
guys are and
ребята и
don't switch video de menthe cover
не переключайте video de menthe cover
damn it
блин
with a
с
fantasy
то и болин 30 жалко